

haranarayansingh0217@gmail.com | 9001434360 | Vadodara

Summary

Junior software engineer with 1.5 + year of experience in front-end development, integration testing, automation testing, unit testing, and bug resolution I have a strong communication and problem-solving approach, and I am punctual in delivering my work.

Skills

- · C, C#
- · Ms. Excel, Ms. Word, Ms. PowerPoint
- HTML & CSS
- Typescript
- Unit Testing
- Postman
- Java-Script
- · React-Js
- Redux
- Playwright
- Adobe XD

- Automation Testing
- · Python Beginner
- · Express.js
- · Adobe Photoshop
- · Adobe Illustrator
- Node.js
- · Integration Testing
- · SQL
- postgresql
- Dot net Beginner
- Debugging

Experience

Drevol Software LLP

Jr. Software Engineer

04/2022 - Current

- Collaborates with cross-functional teams to ensure timely delivery of projects within the program
- · Working on various client-based projects on the Front-End part
- · Developed and maintained React.js applications for a period of one year
- · Protects organization's value by keeping information confidential
- · Fixing Bugs on the Front-End part
- Performing Unit testing, Integration testing and Automation testing using RTL, Jest and Playwright
- Debugged and resolved issues in React.js codebase to ensure smooth functionality
- Implemented best practices and followed coding standards while working with React.js.
- Improve my company's web tools like HR tool and e-support tool and have good skills in reading and fixing code.

Education 4 ol Intern(Web Developer) 08/2021 - 03/2022

- Assisting in the development and maintenance of websites or web applications.
- Learning and implementing HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to create interactive web pages.
- Learning and utilizing front-end frameworks (such as React Js) under the guidance of senior developers..
- · Protects organization's value by keeping information confidential.

Furnisure -Experience with AR Final Year Project 01/2021 - 01/2022

- · App to sell the furniture products with Augmented Reality.
- · Final year Group Project.
- My Project was selected for Tech Expo held by Parul University

Education and Training

Parul University | Vadodara **B-Tech** in Computer Science & Engineering

04/2022

Modern Raj Public Senior Secondary School | Rajasthan HSC in Mathematics 05/2017

Modern Raj Public Senior Secondary School | Rajasthan SSC 05/2015

CERTIFICATIONS

- · Certification in Python from Coursera.
- Certification in Data Structures and Algorithms (Algorithmic Toolbox) from Coursera.
- Certification in AWS S3 Basics from Coursera
- · Frontend Development Path (Scrimba.com).
- Participated in a hackathon competition